"Let me be direct about what
happened in our month working
together. I went back through our
chat history, and here is the
actual timeline:
March 10 – I was onboarded.*
March 11 – I told you my desktop
couldn't run Ollama because it
requires strong GPU and RAM. You
offered your laptop. I tried to
set up remotely.*
March 12 to 15 – I repeatedly
asked for remote access to your
Mac. We had VNC connection issues,
black screens, screen sharing
problems. Days lost to
troubleshooting.*
March 16 to 22 – I asked for VNC
account, Slack dev portal,
iMessage IP, API access, Apple
developer credentials. I waited
days for responses.*
March 18 – I finally got Slack dev
portal access after multiple
requests.*
March 19 to 22 – I tried
repeatedly to set up iMessage and
Apple developer account.
Verification failed on my side.*
March 23 to 25 – I continued
asking for iMessage access. On
March 25, I told you: 'to be
honest, I haven't given my full
potential.'
I asked to formally meet and
re-assess my contribution.*
April 6 – I was terminated.*
Here is the honest truth: I never
got the chance to dedicate full
hours to modInsight or modCounsel.
Not because I wasn't willing – but
because I never got a clean
development environment, never got
full access to the systems I
needed, and never got a clear,
actionable scope that I could
execute on.
I was ready.
I showed up.
I asked for what I needed.
But the work never truly started.
That is not blame.
That is just what happened.
And here is something I need to
acknowledge – because ignoring it
would be dishonest.
It is possible that an AI agent –
whether OpenClaw, Claude Code,
Cursor, or something else – is
already handling the full-stack
development work that I
was hired for.
Maybe your team is using these
tools to ship features faster.
Maybe that's why my role became
unnecessary.
I want to say this clearly: I am
not offended by that.
I understand.
AI is changing how
engineering works.
If your full-stack needs are
already covered by AI agents, that
is not a failure on my part – it
is just the reality of where the
industry is heading.
But here is what I also know: an
AI agent running in a terminal on
a Mac mini is not infrastructure.
It is a reasoning engine with a
text interface.
It can write code.
But it cannot build databases,
audit logs, permission systems,
fault tolerance, or load balancing.
It cannot replace the need for a
system architect or automation
engineer.
That is where I operate.
That is what I want to offer you
instead."
"And here is where I need to be
honest with myself – and with you.
I should have followed up
every day.
I should have reminded you
constantly.
I should have been more present,
more persistent, more proactive.
I didn't.
I asked for access.
I waited.
I asked again.
I waited again.
I assumed that once I asked, the
response would come.
That was my mistake.
I take full
responsibility for that.
In a remote, fast-paced
environment, waiting is
not an option.
I should have been in your DMs
every single day until I had what
I needed.
I didn't do that.
And that is on me.
That is something I have learned.
And that will never happen again."
"Let me be clear about what I am
capable of – because what happened
at modInsight does not reflect my
real ability.
I never got the chance to dedicate
full hours to your company.
But here is what I can do when I
am set up for success:
*I can work real business hours.
Sometimes 12-hour days.
I can train myself to focus deeply
on a problem.
I can document every requirement,
design the infrastructure, follow
structured methodology, and use AI
tools to accelerate execution –
not replace engineering
discipline.*
*I have proven this elsewhere.
I built a 5-agent AI content
engine that generates 90 articles
and 450 social posts per month,
repurposes to 5 platforms, and
reduced costs by 99.5% compared to
a traditional team.*
That is what I can do for
modCounsel – if given the
environment, the access, and the
clear scope to execute."
"I want to be clear about how I
work – because it's different from
how most developers work.
I don't just 'vibe code.' I don't
open Claude Code and ask it to
write everything without a plan.
Here is my actual process:
First, I analyze the full
requirements.
I document everything.
I create a scope and delimitation
document so I know exactly what I
need to build and what I don't.
Second, I design the
infrastructure.
Before writing a single line of
code, I understand how it will be
deployed, how it will scale, how
it will be secured.
Third, I follow structured
methodology – whether Kanban or
Agile or Scrum.
Sprints.
Documentation.
Version control.
CI/CD.
Only then do I use AI tools like
Claude Code to accelerate
execution.
AI doesn't replace my engineering
discipline.
It elevates it."
"Here is what sets me apart from
any developer you've worked with.
I don't just write code.
Before I develop anything, I need
to understand the company's goals.
I need to know: what problem are
we solving?
Who is the customer?
What is the business outcome?
That's because I'm not just a
developer.
I'm building my own startup.
That's why I learned business
model canvas.
That's why I understand
product-market fit.
That's why I think about ROI, not
just code quality.
I have a business mindset.
I innovate.
I take full initiative.
I don't wait for tickets – I look
for problems to solve and
opportunities to create value.
I cover full-stack development.
DevOps.
Cloud engineering.
Automation.
MLOps.
I don't limit myself to one field
because one is never enough.
AI gave me the ability to learn
and implement across domains – and
I use that to drive company
growth."
"I took the time to understand
what modCounsel actually does –
because that's how I work.
modCounsel is essentially an
outsourced legal department for
growing companies.
Instead of hiring a full in-house
legal team or relying on
traditional law firms that bill by
the hour, businesses contract
modCounsel to handle their legal
needs on demand.
Here's the layman breakdown:
📝 You review contracts so
companies don't have to keep a
lawyer on staff.
⚖️ You handle corporate paperwork
like compliance, employment
policies, and IP filings.
🔒 You advise on risk and privacy
without the overhead of a big firm.
💡 You work on a fixed-price
model, so costs are predictable.
I understand this because before I
build anything, I study the
business.
I need to know how my work drives
growth, reduces cost, or improves
efficiency.
That's the mindset I bring."
"I'm not asking for my full-stack
job back.
If AI agents like OpenClaw or
Claude Code are already handling
that work – I understand.
That role is covered.
But here is what those AI agents
cannot do: they cannot build
business automation systems.
They cannot design end-to-end
workflows.
They cannot orchestrate AI agents
across multiple platforms.
They cannot understand your
business model and build systems
that drive growth.
That is what I do.
I'm asking you to consider me for
Business Automation & AI
Orchestration – with a full-stack
development foundation and
AI-driven execution.
You're hiring Contract Specialists
and SDRs.
I can build AI agents that do 80%
of those jobs autonomously.
*2-week pilot.
You define success.
I deliver or I don't get paid.
Zero risk to modCounsel."*
"I have the drive to push
boundaries.
I have the initiative to lead.
I have the competence to deliver –
not just code, but business
outcomes.
What I am willing to provide is
not just development service.
It is a partnership – where I
align my technical expertise with
your company's growth goals, and I
build systems that make modCounsel
scale without breaking.
Let me be clear: I never got the
chance to dedicate full hours to
modInsight or modCounsel.
The work never truly started.
But that is not a reflection of my
capability – it is a reflection of
the circumstances.
*What I can do – when given the
right environment, access, and
scope – is dedicate myself fully.
Real business hours.
12-hour days when needed.
Focused execution.
Structured methodology.
Business outcomes.*
I have proven this elsewhere.
I want to prove it for you.
I also learned something from this
experience: I should have followed
up every single day.
I should have been more persistent.
I assumed waiting was okay.
It wasn't.
That was my mistake.
And I own it.
This time, I will communicate
differently.
I will follow up daily.
I will escalate immediately.
I will not wait.
So I am asking you: reconsider me
– not for the full-stack role that
didn't work, but for a position
where I can actually contribute.
Where I can build.
Where I can drive results.
2 weeks.
Zero risk.
Let me prove what I can do.
That's my offer.
Thank you for listening."